

Chuck Combs MSN, FNP

Professional Summary

Qualified medical professional with years of experience in a leadership nursing role with training in patient education and leadership.

Self-directed and solutions-oriented with fantastic communication skills.

Committed to increasing the quality of patient care through top-of-the-line time management and prioritization.

Focused on helping patients manage issues and improve health. Open and caring healthcare team member with advanced understanding of geriatric and behavioral health care.

Proficient ability to conduct physical examinations, order and interpret labs and prescribe appropriate treatments or medications to treat chronic and acute conditions. Knowledgeable about educating patients on treatments and disease prevention.

Work History

Desert Haven Behavioral Health - Director Of Nursing

Phoenix, Arizona

01/2019 - Current

Manage and lead all nursing personnel operations.

Develop short and long-term goals for the entire nursing department.

Develop, implement. and support nursing guidelines and policies.

Plan and oversee admission, nursing, and patient care processes.

Respond to any nursing-related issues in a timely manner.

Investigate and resolve resident, family and associates concerns.

Coordinate with medical associates and other departments to ensure facility efficiency and optimal resident care.

Oversee and audit all record-keeping processes and ensure all necessary documents are accurate and up-to-date.

Hire and train new nursing staff members.

Evaluate associate performance and support improvement when necessary.

Coordinate and lead resident care plan meetings.

Copper Village Memory Care - Director Of Nursing Mesa, AZ 01/2016 - 01/2017

psychnurs@hotmail.com (480) 522-0260 3035 East Vernon St, Gilbert, AZ 85298

Skills

Certified MANDT Behavior Management
Certified Nursing Leadership
Certified CPR/First Aid Instructor
Certified in Long Term Care
Proficient in 5 star quality measures
Quality Assurance and performance
improvement Process
Proficient in MS Office
Proficient in EMR and Cerner software
Industry Speaker

Education

2010

University of Phoenix Tempe, AZ

Bachelor of Science: Nursing

2019

Purdue University

Westville, IN

Master of Science: Nursing in Family Nurse Practitioner

Maravilla Care Center - Director Of Education

Phoenix, Arizona

01/2015 - 01/2016

Design and implement educational programs.

Develops curriculum or content for classes, lectures, conferences, or other educational materials.

Oversee and audit the operations of certification or credentialing programs.

Ensures that all activities and requirements regarding an organization's education/certification programs are met.

CPR instructor

Maravilla Care Center - Assistant Director Of Nursing Phoenix, Arizona 01/2011 - 01/2015

Maravilla Care Center - Charge Nurse

Phoenix, Arizona

01/2010 - 01/2011

Record patients' medical records and monitor vital signs.

Supervising nursing staff and monitoring their needs.

Coordinating daily administrative duties, including schedules, nursing assignments and patient care.

Overseeing patient admissions, transfers and discharges.

Mentoring and training new staff and providing support and guidance to all staff members.

Monitoring medical charts and providing compassionate care and assistance to patients and families.

Liaising with doctors and administrators and communicating any protocol changes to staff.

Ensuring compliance with all health and safety regulations.

Recording and maintaining accurate reports.

Identifying issues or emergencies and responding in a calm and efficient manner.